mylicindia.com 2012-12-09

# Privacy Policy | LIC of India

Topics:      

Your privacy is important to [www.mylicindia.com](http://www.mylicindia.com/ "www.mylicindia.com") (hereinafter referred to as the “website”). This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that the website collects, and the ways in which the website uses that personal information.

###  **Personal information collection**

 **The website may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:**

  * information about your use of this website (including browsing patterns and behavior);
  * information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website for updates and newsletter (including contact details);
  * When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address or both
  * information about transactions carried out over this website;
  * information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services (including SMS and email alerts); and
  * Any other information that you send to fellow users and webmaster.

###  **Using personal information**

 **The website may use your personal information to:**

  * administer this website;
  * personalize the website for you;
  * enable your access to and use of the website services;
  * publish information about you on the website;
  * Send you marketing communications via email/SMS.

Where the website discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.  
In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, the website may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

###  **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

###  **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.mylicindia.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.mylicindia.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Commission Junction  
Adbrite  
Clickbank  
Linkshare  
Kontera  
DGM-India

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.mylicindia.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.mylicindia.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.mylicindia.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

###  **Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

###  **Securing of your data**

The website will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.  
The website will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

###  **Cross-border data transfers**

Information that the website collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which the website operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.  
In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.  
You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

###  **Updating this statement**

The website may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.  
You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

###  **Contact Webmaster**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the website’s treatment of your personal information, please write to:  
Webmaster at mylicindia.com

 **This privacy statement**  
This privacy statement is based on an original template created by website-contracts.co.uk and distributed by freenetlaw.com  

Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC of India) is the largest insurance company in India. LIC of India was founded in 1956 with the merger of 200 insurance companies. Currently, LIC has Rs.9.31 trillion worth of assets. Its fully owned by Govt. of India and LIC funds about 1/4th of government expenses. 

LIC of India is no doubt the most trusted insurance company in India. LIC India has various insurance plans to suit your needs from child insurance to pension plan. 

Top Insurance Plans  
Note: This is NOT an Official LIC Website. We are authorized LIC Agents. This website is meant for General information only. For any Dispute, please contact info at mylicinda.com You are requested to read our disclaimer and Privacy policy.   
lic india, india insurance, insurance india, india, lic, lic india, lic of india, india lic, life insurance, life insurance india, lic policy.
